golocal247.com 2017-02-24

# GoLocal247 - Yellow Pages, Local Business Directory, Coupons, Events, Classifieds, Community Portal - Golocal247.com

**_PRIVACY POLICY_**

The User-Friendly Phone Book (“User-Friendly”) has a firm commitment to privacy and created this privacy statement to disclose our privacy policies which include how your personal information is gathered, used, and disseminated for use through 247.com (the “Web Site”) this Web Site. This privacy policy applies only to information collected or obtained through this Web Site and not information obtained by other means. User-Friendly understands the importance of ensuring that your personal information is secure and protected and uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect personal information from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure. We will not use or sell your personal information to third parties at any time unless when legally required to do so to cooperate with governmental authorities investigating claims of illegal activity which includes but is not limited to; illegal transfer of copyrighted material, Web Site postings or email messages containing threats of violence or as detailed below. We may also disclose personally identifiable information in other cases where we have reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use.

**Personal Information and Member Registration.**  
To receive community services and membership benefits, the Web Site maintains a limited amount of your personal information given during Registration. The information provided prevents others from using the same log-in or Message Board(s) Screen Name. As registration on the site is completely voluntary, the user has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The type of information requested or collected by us includes: user contact information (name, email address, street address, phone number, log-in name password and screen name) and user demographic information (gender or age). The Web Site may also collect personal information from you if you choose to participate in activities such as sweepstakes, contests, games, surveys or because you want us to furnish you with products, services, newsletters, or information in connection with your use of social networking sites and public areas, or in connection with content or suggestions you submit to the Web Site.

**Use of Personal Information.**

User-Friendly will only use the Personal Information you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If User-Friendly obtains Personal Information from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is also governed by this Privacy Policy. User-Friendly may share your Personal Information with companies that are affiliated with us, provided you have given us permission.

User-Friendly will not share your credit card information with third parties except those User-Friendly uses to perform tasks required to complete purchases you make through the Web Site. User-Friendly employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your Personal Information. User-Friendly may share your Personal Information with outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities including but not limited to; message boards, sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment and data processing, or with outside contractors, agents or sponsors who help us with administration, judging and prize fulfillment aspects of contests, sweepstakes and games. These outside contractors, agents, or sponsors may only use your Personal Information to provide User-Friendly with a specific service and not for any other purpose without your consent. User-Friendly may also provide your Personal Information to a third party in those instances where you have chosen to receive certain information and have been notified that the fulfillment of such a request requires the sharing of your Personal Information.

User-Friendly may aggregate Personal Information and use it anonymously. Anonymous click stream, number of page views, calculated web beacons, and aggregated demographic information may also be shared with User-Friendly’s advertisers and business partners.

**Access to Personal Information.**  
User demographic information collected will be used by us to tailor a visitor’s experience at our Web Site showing and displaying content according to their preferences or content which we think a user might like and may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis in a manner that will not personally identify the individual submitting such information.

The information you entrust to us is protected on a secure web server and we have made and will continue to make substantial efforts to achieve a well protected environment. However, we - nor any Web Site operator - can completely guarantee that your information will be immune from unauthorized access.

Although your Registration and Profile information is always confidential, all listing submissions and postings to the public pages of the Web Site is available for all users to view and is considered public content for general viewing. Therefore, this information is not private or held in confidence. We urge you to always use caution and discretion when posting any personally identifying information about yourself or your household.

The Web Site may collect other non-Personal Information including IP address, aggregate user data, and browser type. This data is used to manage and improve the Services, track usage, and for security and monitoring purposes.

**Cookies.**  
The Web Site makes use of browser “Cookies” and therefore registered members are required to have Cookies enabled on their computers. Cookies are files written to a user’s hard disk and read by the server programs to inform a website if the user has previously visited that site. Enabling Cookies will allow you to access your registered member profile and my247.com membership page; it will allow for delivery of content specific to you interests, to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site and for other purposes. Cookies can be rejected by you and if so none of the functions listed above will be performed.

Third-Party advertisements and links displayed on the Services may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers. The Web Site does not control these cookies and users of the Services should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies.

**Linking and Framing.**

This site contains links to other sites and is not responsible for content, privacy practices or security measures of such websites. When linking to another site you may still see our site’s logo or frame, however, you are no longer on the Web Site and are now on a different website whose information collection practices may differ from ours and therefore, the privacy policy of the site you are on will govern how information collected from you is used.

**Public Forums.**  
The Web Site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups and/or social networking sites available to its users. Any information disclosed in these areas or to these sites becomes public information and User-Friendly cannot accept any responsibility for ensuring the privacy of information you choose to disclose in these areas or to these sites.

**Web Site Use and Rights.**  
Posting communications on or through the Web Site automatically grants User-Friendly a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive license to use, reproduce, modify, publish, edit, translate, distribute, perform, and display the information alone or as part of other works in any form, media, or technology whether now known or hereafter developed. The foregoing grants shall include the right to exploit any proprietary rights in such communication, including but not limited to rights under copyright, trademark, service mark or patent laws under any relevant jurisdiction.

**Liability Disclaimer.**  
User-Friendly specifically disclaims any liability with regard to any actions resulting from your submissions and postings to the public portion of the Web Site. Generally, any communication which you post to the Web Site is considered to be non-confidential and must comply with the Terms of Service.

**Security.  
**This Web Site has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please remember that no computer system should be considered safe from intrusion. ** **

**Opt-Out/Unsubscribe Provision.**

Users are provided the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our Web Site by clicking on the unsubscribe link generated at the bottom of all email messages received. Simply click on the unsubscribe link to go to a page that allows you to unsubscribe from any or all of the lists to which you are subscribed.

**Correct/Update.**

If you would like to change or modify previously provided information, please send an email to the Web Site administrator at [webadmin@golocal247.com](mailto:webadmin@golocal247.com?subject=Inquiry%3A%20Privacy%20Policy "mailto:webadmin@golocal247.com").

**Contacting the Web Site.**

For questions about this privacy statement or site practices, please contact the following:

            GoLocal247.com Administrator

            10200 Grogan’s Mill Road, STE 440

            The Woodlands, TX 77380

            administrator@247.com

**Changes to Privacy Policy.**  
User-Friendly may make changes to this policy from time to time. All changes to the policy will be posted. Registered Members will be notified by email of any significant changes.
